{
    "id": "1f21de21330141c58657382068d5e803",
    "title": "Idiomatic Expressions",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His activities are always ……………….. suspicion",
            "description": "If your actions are above suspicion, nobody will suspect you of doing something wrong",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "below"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "944be2a8498b478a9b0eb0a1cfef3c72"
        },
        {
            "question": "How are you going to account ........................... your absence at the meeting?",
            "description": "To account for something is to provide a satisfactory explanation for something.",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "to",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d19c8775a2947ee9a1d22cb50a5685a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The job interview was very easy and I am sure that I ................................ it.",
            "description": "To ace something is to do exceptionally well in a tough situation.",
            "answers": [
                "clicked",
                "aced",
                "hacked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1316df85c354555a103742c535a6647"
        },
        {
            "question": "The No-confidence motion was an .............................. test for the Prime Minister",
            "description": "An acid test is a test where conclusions are beyond doubt.",
            "answers": [
                "acid",
                "fire",
                "sour"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "161581dfed524e04a6a05f7c2d002cc9"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ................................... a taste for ballet during her trip to Spain.",
            "description": "To acquire a taste for something is to start liking it.",
            "answers": [
                "gained",
                "earned",
                "acquired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "434dbe07c3ed4a0aab53ddd78ca5e8f2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wages have increased ................................. the board.",
            "description": "If something happens across the board, it is applicable to everyone equally.",
            "answers": [
                "along",
                "across",
                "through"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2531dd510a9448dbf61fcd2e14a2cc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her friend often teases her for not .................................. her age.",
            "description": "To act your age is to act as a mature person.",
            "answers": [
                "behaving",
                "acting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "203c5d237ea14f339d07b080e0ca4b36"
        },
        {
            "question": "That child has started acting ............................... again.",
            "description": "To act up is to misbehave.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "500311d67db44609a3f2202afa6cf99d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The things that she said about your boyfriend do not ............................... to anything.",
            "description": "If things do not add up, they do not mean anything.",
            "answers": [
                "add up",
                "add in",
                "add on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "97ff4ec47ade46a3b8cbb2dec05ca8a3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Dad advised me ..................................... buying a new car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c414651fe9cb47c0b86f6a9f0416980a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is afraid of his own .................................",
            "description": "To be easily frightened.",
            "answers": [
                "shadow",
                "friend",
                "shade"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "753d877587e8437194d5f33341ef40d5"
        }
    ]
}